tabsite.com 2019-03-30

# TabSite | Promotions Apps to Grow Leads and Engagement

## Who we are

Our website address is: [https://www.tabsite.com](https://www.tabsite.com/blog).

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Information Gathering and Usage

When you register for TabSite we ask for information such as your name, company name, email address, billing address, credit card information. Members who sign up for the Free Plan are not required to enter a credit card. Those who signup for Free Trials are required to give a credit card.

TabSite by Digital Hill uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Disqus is used for commenting on the site. Disqus privacy policy: <https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy>.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

Analytics collected on this site are collected by Google Analytics. Google Analytics tracks where you came from by your IP address location. Google Analytics privacy policy: <https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html>

## Who we share your data with

Digital Hill uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run TabSite. Although Digital Hill owns the code, databases, and all rights to the TabSite application, you retain all rights to your data.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. When you sign up to be on our email list, for marketing purposes, your data is stored in MailChimp. MailChimp does not use the data.

## Contact information

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to info (at)DigitalHill(dot)com or by mail to: Digital Hill, 229 S. Main St. Goshen, IN 46526.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

If there would be a breach of data, we would correct the breach and personally email the recipients within 48 hours.

### Disclosure

TabSite or Digital Hill may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.
